There is a group in Europe that seems fundamentaly unable
to coexist with greater society.
The members of this group are disproportionately violent
as indicated by crime statistics.
Most cases of vandalism can also be chalked up to them
and if there is any violent crime committed in your area,
and members of this group live there, you can be certain
it was them.
It's time to break the silence. We need to talk openly about
this group and their degenerate behavior.
Namely:
men
Now look, I know what you're thinking.
Adam, I know and like plenty of men in my life and they
aren't all violent savages.
The actions of some bad men shouldn't be used to
condemn the entire group.
To which I say: why don't you try to live around them for a bit
before making your cucked men's rights activist arguments.
See how you'll like them after they stab you in the throat for
a cigarette or rob your house or beat you up for looking at them wrong.
Sometimes, men even band together into large, violent groups that
wreak havok and burn down cities.
Sometime due to the most innocuous things, like their favorite
football team losing a match or something.
Of course to be fair some women also commit violent crime, some
of them also damage public property, but just look at the
prison population: 9 out of 10 violent crime inmates are men.
Now I'm not sexist. I myself have male friends. I'm only interested
in making our communities safer
and the logical solution to that is to get rid of the group that's
responsible for all the violence.
Therefore I advocate for rounding up all the men, putting them in
specific residential areas within a city,
preferably around the edge somewhere, and then building a wall to
segregate them from the rest of us
to keep our cities safe from their criminal, violent nature.
Right...
So the solution you've just listened to, despite being absolutely
preposterous, would be an extremely effective tool
at curtailing violent crime.
However, we never hear it from the crowd most obsessed with
law and order.
Men as a group never seem to come up despite being disproportionately
violent.